[
    {
        "front": "スーパー",
        "back": "supermarket",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "セール",
        "back": "sale",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほとんど",
        "back": "most (of)",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "しなもの\n「品物」",
        "back": "articles",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "わりびき\n「割引」",
        "back": "discount",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんがく\n「半額」",
        "back": "half price",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "うれしい",
        "back": "glad",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "とくに\n「特に」",
        "back": "in particular",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "れいとう（する）\n「冷凍」",
        "back": "freezing / to freeze",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくひん\n「食品」",
        "back": "food",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "科なら\n「科なら」",
        "back": "to be sure to",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "のこる\n「凝る」",
        "back": "to be left",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "たりる\n「足りる」",
        "back": "to be enough, be sufficient",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）たす\n「足す」",
        "back": "to add",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんや\n「今夜」",
        "back": "tonight",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようい（する）\n「用意」",
        "back": "preparations / to prepare",
        "chapter": "N4 C1"
    }
]